Jon Pour

(C) 425-299-1292 | Jonpour9@Gmail.com | Everett, WA 98201

## SUMMARY

Hardworking with excellent materials handling, storage management and shipment preparation skills. Experienced in picking orders, assembling pallets and preparing containers. Accustomed to facilitating accurate inventory counts and maintaining current warehouse records.

Results-driven sales leader bringing demonstrated record of progressive growth and accomplishments. Proactive manager and strategic problem-solver with record of achieving challenging profit goals while consistently acquiring new customers and expanding operations. Tenacious in pursuing new revenue streams and sales opportunities.

## **SKILLS**

Safety conscious
Pallet jack and hand truck operation
Skilled forklift operator
Route management
Over the road experience
Energetic self-starter
B2B sales and customer service
Territory and account management
Team player mentality
Product Sales

## **EXPERIENCE**

Auditor, Gigwalk Inc., June 2019-Current San Francisco, CA

Facilitated successful internal and external audits through sound and thorough documentation. Provided suggestions to improve management control weaknesses. Identified weaknesses of existing control systems and made suggestions for remediation.

Shuttle Driver, Hallcon Corporation, December 2017-June 2019 Kansas City, KS

Planned efficient routes and adjusted plans using GPS software and local road knowledge.

Planned efficient routes and adjusted strategies based on current weather and traffic information.

Completed efficient transfers at hubs and final destinations to keep routes on schedule.

Delivery Driver, Service Partners LLC, November 2015-November 2017 Marysville, WA

Safely operated and maintained heavy equipment, including forklifts, stair climbers and pallet jacks.

Directed efficient product loading and checked load balance to prevent on-the-road incidents. Obtained signatures needed to complete and process all paperwork efficiently.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Liberal Arts And General Studies, Spokane Community College, Spokane WA